wordtracker.com 2015-05-02

# Wordtracker's privacy policy

reveal high-performing keywords in minutesreveal high-performing keywords in minutesreveal high-performing keywords in minutesreveal high-performing keywords in minutesreveal high-performing keywords in minutes best keywordsbest keywordsbest keywordsbest keywordsbest keywords keywords competitionkeywords competitionkeywords competitionkeywords competitionkeywords competition keywordskeywordskeywordskeywordskeywords top keywords by competitiontop keywords by competitiontop keywords by competitiontop keywords by competitiontop keywords by competition reveal high-performing keywords in minutesreveal high-performing keywords in minutesreveal high-performing keywords in minutesreveal high-performing keywords in minutesreveal high-performing keywords in minutes best keywordsbest keywordsbest keywordsbest keywordsbest keywords keywords competitionkeywords competitionkeywords competitionkeywords competitionkeywords competition keywordskeywordskeywordskeywordskeywords top keywords by competitiontop keywords by competitiontop keywords by competitiontop keywords by competitiontop keywords by competition reveal high-performing keywords in minutesreveal high-performing keywords in minutesreveal high-performing keywords in minutesreveal high-performing keywords in minutesreveal high-performing keywords in minutes best keywordsbest keywordsbest keywordsbest keywordsbest keywords keywords competitionkeywords competitionkeywords competitionkeywords competitionkeywords competition keywordskeywordskeywordskeywordskeywords top keywords by competitiontop keywords by competitiontop keywords by competitiontop keywords by competitiontop keywords by competition reveal high-performing keywords in minutesreveal high-performing keywords in minutesreveal high-performing keywords in minutesreveal high-performing keywords in minutesreveal high-performing keywords in minutes best keywordsbest keywordsbest keywordsbest keywordsbest keywords keywords competitionkeywords competitionkeywords competitionkeywords competitionkeywords competition keywordskeywordskeywordskeywordskeywords top keywords by competitiontop keywords by competitiontop keywords by competitiontop keywords by competitiontop keywords by competition reveal high-performing keywords in minutesreveal high-performing keywords in minutesreveal high-performing keywords in minutesreveal high-performing keywords in minutesreveal high-performing keywords in minutes best keywordsbest keywordsbest keywordsbest keywordsbest keywords keywords competitionkeywords competitionkeywords competitionkeywords competitionkeywords competition keywordskeywordskeywordskeywordskeywords top keywords by competitiontop keywords by competitiontop keywords by competitiontop keywords by competitiontop keywords by competition

We respect your privacy and do not tolerate spam and will never sell, rent, lease or give away your information (name, address, email, etc.) to any third party. Nor will we send you unsolicited email.

If you choose to give your name and email address into one or more of our site's registration forms, then we will send you emails relating to the mailing list(s) or service(s) you joined and the Keyword Expert newsletter, as well as marketing offers from time to time. You may opt out of receiving future mailings from our mailing lists; see the choice/opt-out section below.

#### Financial information

Financial information (such as credit card number and expiration date) is used only to charge you for the service you are purchasing. This will never be given to any third party (other than the credit card authorization processors [Secure Trading](http://securetrading.com/) and [Wirecard](http://www.wirecard.com/)). 

#### How do we protect your information?

In order to prevent unauthorized access, Wordtracker uses strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information which you have given to us. We take all reasonable precautions to ensure the security of personal data stored on our system.

All your personal information is password-protected - only registered users and Wordtracker support staff have access to this information. As a registered user, you will be able to edit or delete your personal information details at any time using your own ID and password.

#### Does Wordtracker share information?

Your personal information is being provided only to Wordtracker unless we specifically state otherwise. We will not disclose your personally identifiable information to any person or company except where you have given us permission to do so or if the law requires it, or where in good faith Wordtracker believes such action is necessary to comply with a legal process.

#### What about cookies?

As you browse Wordtracker.com, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Our display advertising partner, AdRoll, then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with Wordtracker.com.

The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number. You can [visit this page to opt out of AdRoll and their partners’ targeted advertising](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/). 

Read all about our cookie policy here.

#### Choice/opt-out

If you would like to be removed from our database, please let us know. If you wish to stop receiving the Keyword Expert newsletter or any of our mailing lists, please use the unsubscribe link in an email from each list.

#### Children

Wordtracker is not structured to attract children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age. If we are made aware that information is or has been submitted by or collected from a child aged 12 or younger, we will delete this information.

#### Contacting us

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of the Wordtracker web site, or your dealings with this web site, please [contact us](http://www.wordtracker.com/contact). 

#### Publicly available information

If you post any personally identifiable information in a Wordtracker blog, forum etc, then this may be displayed publicly.

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy came into effect in 1998 and was last updated on 23rd September 2008. Any updates to this policy will be published on this page.
